<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on DEV - 0 A.D. | A free, open-source game of ancient warfare</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on DEV - 0 A.D. | A free, open-source game of ancient warfare</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Release: 0 A.D. Alpha 25: Yaunā</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/new-release-0ad-alpha-25-yauana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/new-release-0ad-alpha-25-yauana/</guid><description>Wildfire Games proudly announces the release of 0AD Alpha 25: “Yaunā,” the twenty-fifth alpha version of 0 A.D., a free, open-source real-time strategy game of ancient warfare. Yaunā is an old Persian word for Ionians (Greeks).
Trailers Youtube:
PeerTube:
New Features in Alpha 25 Pathfinding And Netcode Improvements – Improved Pathfinding, Performance And Reduced Game Lag Order Restructuring – Players Can Now Push New Orders To The Front Of Their Production Queues Improved Unit AI New Biomes Incorporating New 2k Textures And Normal/Specular Maps Initial Implementation Of Single Player Campaigns GUI Improvements Extended Graphics Options Improved Mod Support And Game Filtering In The Multiplayer Lobby Ongoing Civilization Balancing Various Other Game Stability Bug Fixes And Speedups Easy download and install Download and installation instructions are available for Windows, Linux and macOS.</description></item><item><title>0 A.D. Alpha 25 Feature Freeze Update</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/alpha-25-feature-freeze-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/alpha-25-feature-freeze-update/</guid><description>The date of 6th June 2021 at 23.59 CET has been confirmed for the 0 A.D. Alpha 25 Feature Freeze, a major precursor to the actual release of the new alpha version of the game.
What is the Feature Freeze? The Feature Freeze is the point at which new features cease to be added to the new alpha version and the development team focus solidly on final preparations and bugfixes to facilitate the release.</description></item><item><title>Sneak Peek of 0 A.D. Alpha 25</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/sneak-peek-alpha-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/sneak-peek-alpha-25/</guid><description>A provisional date of June 2021 has been proposed for the ‘Feature Freeze’ – the point at which new features for the upcoming Alpha version of 0 A.D. stop being added and the development team focus solidly on bugfixes. This is not the release date. The feature freeze is one of the precursors to release, with the specific launch date to follow. You can find more information here.
First Impressions of Alpha 25 Be sure to tune into the Tom0AD live stream on YouTube on Friday 7th May 2021 at 9pm CET to see a preview of the latest development version of Alpha 25 in action.</description></item></channel></rss>