<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on DEV - 0 A.D. | A free, open-source game of ancient warfare</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on DEV - 0 A.D. | A free, open-source game of ancient warfare</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>0 A.D. Factions</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/factions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/factions/</guid><description>Edit 2018-09-09: This content may be outdated. We hope to make a new website soon, which will be easier to maintain.
The first edition of 0 A.D. will allow the player to control any of twelve ancient civilizations from the pre-common era. Each culture will be represented at the peak of its civilization, somewhere along the timeline of 500 B.C. to 1 B.C.
Though a momentous task, we are working to ensure that each culture provides a unique yet balanced gameplay experience.</description></item><item><title>0 A.D. Features</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/features/</guid><description>0 A.D. (pronounced “zero ey-dee”) is a free real-time strategy (RTS) game of ancient warfare. Lead a civilization set in the imaginary year of 0 A.D., develop a thriving city, raise a mighty army and contend with rivals for hegemony of the world. History is yours for the taking!
Check out some of the most exciting features in 0 A.D.:
Intense Gameplay Cross-platform: 0 A.D. is set to run on Windows, Linux and OS X.</description></item><item><title>0 A.D. Game Manual</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/game-manual/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/game-manual/</guid><description>Game Objectives and Rules In a nutshell, in 0 A.D., you start out with three things:
Buildings, such as civic centers, Units, such as female citizens and male soldiers, that you can move around the map and use to gather resources, build or fight, and Some initial amounts of four resources: Food, Wood, Stone and Metal. In 0 A.D., you need to gather more of these four resources, and then use them to train (create) various units at your buildings.</description></item><item><title>0 A.D. Project Overview</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/project-overview/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/project-overview/</guid><description>0 A.D. (pronounced “zero-ey-dee”) is a free, open-source, historical Real Time Strategy (RTS) game currently under development by Wildfire Games, a global group of volunteer game developers. As the leader of an ancient civilization, you must gather the resources you need to raise a military force and dominate your enemies.
History is Yours for the Taking
“0 A.D.” is a time period that never actually existed: In the usual calendar, one goes from 1 B.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/contact-us/</guid><description>I have a technical problem with 0 A.D.! We’re sorry you’ve been running into problems with 0 A.D.
It’s a work in progress, so it can be buggy sometimes.
Please read the support page to find ways for us to try to figure it out together.
I want to help out! Great! Thanks! Please read the following:
If you would like to help program the game, you’re invited to get your feet wet and get involved.</description></item><item><title>Contributors</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/contributors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/contributors/</guid><description>0 A.D. is a collaborative project developed by Wildfire Games, a group of contributors from all over the world.
The full list of past and current contributors to 0 A.D. can be found in the game, by clicking the Credits button in the main menu. You can browse the corresponding files containing the list of contributors here: Credits files.
If you have contributed to 0 A.D. but are missing from the lists, please let us know on this forum thread and we will make sure you are included in the credits.</description></item><item><title>Download 0 A.D</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/download/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/download/</guid><description>WIP</description></item><item><title>Get Support</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/support/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/support/</guid><description>As 0 A.D. is still in alpha phase, there are still many problems we need to fix and features we need to implement. Nevertheless, you can find support for 0 A.D. from a variety of sources. Take a look — you’re likely to find an answer to every question.
Frequently Asked Questions See the FAQ on the wiki.
Web Forums Register to our forums and ask the people in our active bug reports forum.</description></item><item><title>Legal Notices</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/legal-notices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/legal-notices/</guid><description>Disclaimer Although the authors (hereafter “Wildfire Games”) tried to make sure this website is free from inaccuracies, and relied on sources believed to be reputable, the information in this website is not necessarily complete, accurate or timely in all instances. Similarly, all links to websites are for information purposes only and are not warranted for content, accuracy, or any other purpose. Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind.</description></item><item><title>Official Logos</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/official-logos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/official-logos/</guid><description>You are invited to spread the word about 0 A.D. using the logos below:
Wildfire Games logo with caption: Wildfiregames logo, SVG format, in ZIP file.
“0 A.D.” is set in Exocet; “Wildfire Games” is in Akzidenz-Grotesk Extended BE. Neither of these fonts is available under a free license.
We like to use Gentium Basic, available under the SIL Open Font License, 1.1.
Please, use these logos only in order to link to the 0 A.</description></item><item><title>Organization</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/organization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/organization/</guid><description>Project Leader Nicolas Auvray (Itms) Administrative Leader Erik Johansson (feneur) Department Heads Johnathan Good (LordGood) – Art Omri Lahav (OmriLahav) – Music Treasury Committee Erik Johansson (feneur) Aviv Sharon (Jeru) Project Liaison to Software in the Public Interest, Inc. Aviv Sharon (Jeru) Last Updated On: 2021-08-19</description></item><item><title>Participate</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/participate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/participate/</guid><description>Everyone is invited to join and contribute to 0 A.D. on a completely voluntary basis, to gain game development experience, to comply with a school project or just for fun.
If you are a programmer, please jump right in and just start offering patches according to the instructions below, and with time we will contact prominent contributors and put them officially on the team. Artists and other contributors can do the same, or just ask to be interviewed and get a volunteer gig in 3d modeling, animating, sound, music etc.</description></item><item><title>The Story of 0 A.D.</title><link>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/the-story-of-0ad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gloviano.github.io/0ad-www-hugo/the-story-of-0ad/</guid><description>A lot of people are surprised to hear that 0 A.D. has been in development since 2001 (or 2003, depending on how you count). What follows is a short history of the project, explaining how it came about and developed into what it is today.
2000-2002: The Birth of 0 A.D. The concept behind 0 A.D. has actually been in the works since the year 2000. It started out as a collaboration between several groups advocating several different ideas.</description></item></channel></rss>